Guide to the Leonid Hurwicz papers, 1911-2008 and undated RL.00599
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research and Writings Series, 1911-2006 and undated, bulk 1945-2006, 142 boxes
  - Other Research and Writings Subseries, 1911-2004 and undated, bulk 1945-2004, 91 boxes
    - Letters, meetings, notes, diagrams, drafts, and publications by others (Box 115)
      - Commitments, travel, 4 folders (Box 115)
      - Mark Walker collaboration, 1983 (Box 115)
      - Impossibility of smooth outcome function (Box 115)
      - Incentives and resource allocation, 7 folders (Box 115)
    - Work by Hurwicz and others, notes and miscellaneous files (Box 116)
      - Papers by others, 13 folders (Box 116)
      - Hurwicz publications and presentations, 19 folders (Box 116)
      - Research notes and miscellaneous files, 6 folders (Box 116)
    - Work by Hurwicz and others (Box 117)
      - Hurwicz writing and notes: decentralization, socialist economies (1975), incentive compatibility, 10 folders (Box 117)
      - Work by others, 10 folders (Box 117)
      - Georgescu-Roegen's notes on Wassily Leontief work, typescript, ca. 1950s (Box 117)
      - Interview with Hurwicz, 1985 (Box 117)
    - Notes and drafts by Hurwicz and others (Box 118)
      - Intertemporal reprints, 8 folders (Box 118)
      - Hurwicz papers (decentralization, institutions, social choice), 1984-1987 (Box 118)
      - Work with Reiter on demand relationships, utility function, 1965-1969 (Box 118)
      - Hurwicz, drafts (sections of unidentified major work), 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box 118)
    - Notes, drafts, and corrections (Box 119)
      - Hurwicz drafts and outlines, 1967-1969, 2002-2004, 11 folders (Box 119)
        Drafts continued from previous box of an unidentified major work; drafts on decentralization.
      - Hurwicz notes and miscellaneous files, 1967 and other dates, 8 folders (Box 119)
      - Notes/drafts, on parameter-indexed product structure..., Walrasian condensation, constructing mechanisms, with Reiter, 2004 (Box 119)
      - Quadratic counter-example, 1996 (Box 119)
      - Reiter (Fran Walker is assistant), editing and notes, 2004 (Box 119)
    - Drafts, notes, collaboration, manuscripts, and publications (Box 120)
      - Drafts (Box 120)
      - Reiter collaboration, faxes from assistant Fran Walker, 2000s, 11 folders (Box 120)
      - Drafts, manuscripts, and publications (Box 120)
      - Notes (Box 120)
    - Notes and works by Hurwicz and others (Box 121)
      - Robert Anderson, Non-Standard Methods in Mathematical Economics, draft, 1990 (Box 121)
      - Hurwicz notes, Walrasian example, 1980 (Box 121)
      - Notes, esp. on HRS (collab. with Reiter and Saari), 11 folders (Box 121)
      - Papers by others (Box 121)
      - Game theory, by Vickrey, with letter to Morgenstern from Vickrey, 1949 (Box 121)
      - Hurwicz notes on Hyers' Linear Topological Spaces, 1945 (Box 121)
    - Drafts and papers, publications, and reprints, 1970s (Box 122)
      - Notes on decentralization, 1959 (Box 122)
      - Optimality, Efficiency, & Resource Allocation (Box 122)
      - Notes and Correspondence (Box 122)
      - Design & Decision Making (Box 122)
      - Others' Published Work (Box 122)
    - Notes, manuscripts, and publications (Box 123)
      - Resource allocation (Box 123)
      - Notes and miscellaneous documents (Box 123)
      - Macroeconomics, Models, Systems, and Structures, 5 folders (Box 123)
    - Notes, drafts, reprints, and original essays (Box 124)
      - Notes and drafts: social/community preference, demand functions (with corr. from Hiro), externalities, 1960s, 9 folders (Box 124)
      - Original essays, 4 folders (Box 124)
      - "Old notes," 1960s? (Box 124)
      - Ann Arbor conference (Box 124)
    - Notes, drafts, reprints, and published papers, chiefly 1960s (Box 125)
      - Reprints (Box 125)
      - Discussion papers by others, chiefly on institutions and economics, with Hurwicz notes, from Tokyo IEA conference, 1987 (Box 125)
      - Hurwicz, Welfare Economics notes (Box 125)
      - Decentralization, notes and drafts, 1980s (Box 125)
      - Collaboration with Anderson, 1948 (Box 125)
      - Weinberger collaboration, 1987 (Box 125)
      - Hurwicz draft and notes, Revisiting Externalities, 1997-1998 (Box 125)
    - Manuscripts,notes, and reprints (Box 126)
      - "Construction of Outcome Functions...," collaboration with David Schmeidler (Box 126)
      - Work with Richter, 1976-1979 (Box 126)
      - International colloquium, 1965 (Box 126)
      - Reprints (Box 126)
    - Notes, presentation materials, and manuscripts (Box 127)
      - Notes and Presentations: Lindahl Equilibrium, Mechanisms, Nash Implementation, 11 folders (Box 127)
      - Manuscripts, collab. with Reiter and others, 5 folders (Box 127)
      - Reprints (Box 127)
      - Notes, teaching, 9 folders (Box 127)
      - Reprints (Box 127)
      - Information and Incentives (Box 127)
      - Informationally Decentralized Pareto-Satisfactory Processes, 1971 (Box 127)
      - Decentralization drafts, 1971-1975 (Box 127)
    - Work with others, notes, drafts, and reprints (Box 128)
      - Work and correspondence with Others: Thomson, Walker, Arrow, Dorfman, 11 folders (Box 128)
      - Reprints (Box 128)
      - Informational requirements, 1976 (Box 128)
      - Dimensional requirements, many notes in thick binder, 1972 (Box 128)
      - Notes on Pivotal Mechanism, 1970s (Box 128)
      - Ville Axioms and Consumer Theory, with Richter, published paper, 1976 (Box 128)
    - Notes, reprints, and manuscripts (Box 129)
      - Krippendorf volume, Interaction between Information and Incentives, 1970s, 2 folders (Box 129)
      - Resource allocation (Box 129)
      - Decentralization (Hurwicz's own work, and with Marschak), 2 folders (Box 129)
      - Hurwicz with Milton Sobel, separation problem, with correspondence exchanges and notes, 1977 (Box 129)
      - Information and incentives (Box 129)
      - Stochastic adjustment with Roy Radner, 1977 (Box 129)
    - Notes, Correspondence, and Miscellaneous (Box 130)
      - Resource allocation (Box 130)
      - Work by others (Box 130)
      - Decentralized Mechanisms, Given Parameter Indexed Product Structures (Box 130)
      - Delegation (Box 130)
    - Reprints, drafts, and notes (Box 131)
      - Reprints of Hurwicz and others, 8 folders (Box 131)
      - Social Norms (Box 131)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, 1989 (Box 131)
      - Walrus and Lindhal, outcome functions (Box 131)
      - Notes and various files, 14 folders (Box 131)
    - Collaborations, notes, and manuscripts (Box 132)
      - Collaboration with Schmeidler, 1977 (Box 132)
      - Collaboration with Uzawa (Box 132)
      - Incentive compatibility and resource allocation, 1975 (Box 132)
      - Notes (Box 132)
      - Integrability and thermodynamics with Richter, 1978 (Box 132)
      - Ville axioms and consumer theory with Richter, 1979 (Box 132)
    - Drafts, reprints, 1970s (Box 133)
      - Jerison, Ville axiom paper, 1990 (Box 133)
      - Law of demand (Box 133)
      - Reiter (Box 133)
      - Draft, Arrow (Box 133)
    - Invited talks, notes, recommended articles and teaching material (Box 134)
      - Economic reform in New Zealand (Box 134)
      - Second fundamental theorem of welfare economics, 1998 (Box 134)
      - Professional papers and curriculum vitae (Box 134)
      - Economic development issues, KDI, 1991-1992 (Box 134)
      - Wooders (Box 134)
    - Drafts, notes, printed material, and teaching material (Box 135)
      Names on folders or in content include: Aitken, Boas, Goebel and Kirk, Ljusternik and Sobolew, Edna Loehman, Mark Kilgour, Rockarfellar (integration theorems), Kornai, Findley and Rodriguez, Sonnenschein, and Wright.
      - Drafts by Hurwicz on Lindahl equilibria, 1996-2002 (Box 135)
      - Complexity chaos encryption (Box 135)
      - Institutional design, notes (Box 135)
      - Notes, 1997 (Box 135)
      - Stanford seminar, 1979 (Box 135)
      - HMP (Hurwicz/Maskin/Postlewaite) (Box 135)
    - Clippings, notes and printed material (Box 136)
      - Game theory (Box 136)
      - Shitovitz, Cores and Competitive Allocations, 2 folders (Box 136)
      - Aumann, Correlated equilibrium (Box 136)
      - Marimon, Lecture notes, 1986, 3 folders (Box 136)
      - Clippings about Soviet Union, China, Eastern Europe economies, 1990s (Box 136)
      - Hurwicz notes on Kihlstrom (Box 136)
    - Drafts, notes on presented papers and other printed material (Box 137)
      Other names on folders include: Jordan, Calsamiglia, Merton, Ostroy, Pratt, Radner.
      - New York City, 1987 (Box 137)
      - Barcelona, 1989 (Box 137)
      - Rochester, 1989 (Box 137)
      - Hicks and others on temporary equilibrium (Box 137)
      - Postlewaite (Box 137)
      - Hurwicz reprint, Survey of Econometrics, 1949 (Box 137)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material, 1980s (Box 138)
      - Carl Simon, notes, 1979 (Box 138)
      - Thompson (Box 138)
      - Summers, 1980 (Box 138)
      - Reprints and articles by many authors: Baumol, Green, Dreze, Kamien, "MOOS," Summers, Sunder, Zechauser (Box 138)
      - Schmeidler, 1981-1982, 3 folders (Box 138)
    - Reprints, articles, a few notes (Box 139)
      Majority are folders with single articles, or mixed folders with photocopied articles, mixed topics. Some appear to be from a S-W series of last names. Includes game theory bibliography.
      - Mark Walker, articles and many Hurwicz notes, includes notes on Lindahl theory (Box 139)
      - Pivotal mechanisms, notes and mention of Clarke (Box 139)
      - Journal of Mathematical Economics, special issue on implementation, 1982 (Box 139)
      - Tian, articles and notes on game theory (Box 139)
    - Correspondence, drafts, notes and various conferences material (Box 140)
      .
      - Dominant strategy implementation article, 1990 (Box 140)
      - Serial cost sharing article, 1991 (Box 140)
      - Lagunoff, Roger, 2 folders (Box 140)
      - Welfare economics (Box 140)
      - Agenda, Committee on Basic Research in the Behavioral Sciences, 1983 (Box 140)
      - Nobel Prize correspondence, 2002 (Box 140)
      - Hammurabi Code (Box 140)
      - Warwick conference, 1999 (Box 140)
    - Conferences, correspondence, notes, printed material and teaching material (Box 141)
      - Library reserve records (Box 141)
      - Second fundamental theorem of welfare economics (Box 141)
      - Braguinsky, correspondence and faxes, 1999 (Box 141)
      - Transparencies, 1983 (Box 141)
      - d'Aspremont and Gerard-Varet, On Bayesian Incentive Compatible Mechanisms, 1979 (Box 141)
      - Various conferences, 1980-1995 (Box 141)
      - On Modeling Institutions, Hurwicz, Barcelona, 1989 (Box 141)
      - Ed Coen, drafts of risk aversion, with some notes and correspondence, 1998 (Box 141)
    - Notes, articles, reports, and correspondence (Box 142)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, many mathematical proofs and exchanges of correspondence, 1990s (Box 142)
      - Sertel, Murat (several folders), mechanism design and other, 1990s (Box 142)
      - Reiter, Mechanism Design, 2004 (Box 142)
      - Papers presented to the U.S. Joint Economic Committee and congressional hearings on Soviet Union and Eastern Europe, 1992 (Box 142)
    - Conferences, notes, and printed material (Box 143)
      - Mixed mathematical notes, models (Box 143)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, 2004 (Box 143)
      - Hurwicz, Condensation procedure for augmental linear product (Box 143)
      - Comparison of Economic Systems (Soviet, Indian, etc.), workshop with notable economists, undated (early 1970s?), 2 folders (Box 143)
      - Hurwicz, Decentralizability in the presence of externalities, 1967 (Box 143)
      - Samuelson, draft of Stochastic asymptotically-homogeneous production functions of maximum large-scale efficiency, 1971 (Box 143)
      - Gillis, Paul, paper on Stokes theorem, 1940, and other paper (Box 143)
      - Statements before Congress, 1970 (Box 143)
      - Wingspread Planning Conference, Academy of Independent Scholars, 1979 (Box 143)
      - Hurwicz, Economic Issues in the Utilization of Knowledge (Box 143)
      - Hurwicz lecture: Conditions for economic efficiency of centralized and decentralized structures, from UC Berkeley symposium on Eastern Europe, 1958 (Box 143)
      - Hurwicz lecture: Between utopia and the status quo (Box 143)
    - Notes and printed material (Box 144)
      - Collaboration with Reiter on Condensation, 1994-1999 (many folders) (Box 144)
      - Notes, Hurwicz,Decentralizability in the presence of externalities, 1966 (Box 144)
      - Hurwicz, Draft Abstract for Institutional change and the theory of mechanism design, circa 1994 (Box 144)
      - Hurwicz, Research Notes on Convergence, 2001 (Box 144)
      - Research notes and drafts, unidentified (Box 144)
      - M. Krein and D. Milman, Extreme points of regular convexity, Hurwicz's notes, 1940s? (Box 144)
    - Notes, drafts, corr., and printed material (Box 145)
      - Notes, Articles, 1940s, 1954 (De Breu) (Box 145)
      - Calculus of Variations, Hurwicz notes, 1940s (Box 145)
      - Other Early Research Notes, Reprints, Articles, 1940s, 1950s, 2 folders (Box 145)
      - Harry Brown, Mathematical concepts, Hurwicz notes (Box 145)
      - Non-separability, 1972 (Box 145)
      - Eastern Europe economy, 1990s (Box 145)
      - HR - Stan Reiter Collaboration, Drafts and Corr., 1999-2004, 3 folders (Box 145)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 146)
      - NY Society for Economic Design, 2002 (Box 146)
      - Rodney Smith, Email and Review of Hurwicz's draft, Externality Problem, 1999-2000 (Box 146)
      - Hurwicz, et al., Feasible Nash implementation of social choice rules... (Box 146)
      - Page Proofs, Japanese Economic Review, 1996 (Box 146)
      - Reprints and Drafts, Institutions, 1987-1994 (Box 146)
      - Roberts, Kevin (Box 146)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 147)
      - Mount and Reiter, 1992 (Box 147)
      - Unpublished draft, Hurwicz, et al. Feasible Nash implementation of social choice rules when the designer does not know endowments or production sets, 1994 (Box 147)
      - Notes for talk, 1995 (Box 147)
      - Implementation, 1990 (Box 147)
      - Montreal transparencies (Box 147)
    - Drafts and printed material (Box 148)
      - Corrected galley proof, Hurwicz, Toward a framework for analyzing institutions and institutional change, 1990 (Box 148)
      - Institutions (Box 148)
      - Green and Lafont, 3 folders (Box 148)
      - Monopolistic competition, 1971 (Box 148)
      - Aoki (Box 148)
      - Evenson (Box 148)
      - Greenberg (Box 148)
    - Chapter drafts, notes and printed material (Box 149)
      - Design of mechanisms for resource allocation, 1972 (Box 149)
      - Informational efficiency (with Reiter), 1990s, 6 folders (Box 149)
      - Informational efficiency, electronic files (2008-0248), 1990s, 6 electronic folders (Box 149)
        Electronic files contain an abstract and drafts of chapters, along with a few other assorted administrative files.
      - Clarke, 1983, 4 folders (Box 149)
      - Sobel, Toel - Bargaining (Box 149)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 150)
      - Articles with Hurwicz annotations and notes: Bergstrom, Azis, Hicks, Kolm Triangle, Kowalik, Kuhn and Tucker, Klee, Scarf, Calsamiglia, Laffont, Wong, Chander, Swanson, Li (Box 150)
      - Reiter Hurwicz collaboration (Box 150)
      - Lagunoff, 1996 (Box 150)
      - Bodswiaz's book, 1991 (Box 150)
    - Notes and printed material (Box 151)
      - Poverty, set of activist memos on Poor People's Campaign (1968), statements, and federal testimony; Galbraith, Tobin, Heller, Pechmann, 1960s (Box 151)
      - Articles by others, often with notes, 1970s-1990s (Box 151)
        Some appear to be in an L-N sequence.
    - Correspondence, foreign language, notes and printed material (Box 152)
      - Cauchy (Box 152)
      - Lindelof (Box 152)
      - Chinese language notes, 8 folders (Box 152)
      - Correspondence (Box 152)
      - Hurwicz/Reiter, notes and draft, 1980s (Box 152)
    - Alphabetical files, notes and printed material (Box 153)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, draft of Chapter 1 (Intro, Parts 1-3), 2001 (Box 153)
      - Alphabetical files, Albertz-Campbell (Box 153)
        Files include Aumann, Balas, Bannerjee, Bauer, Bergstrom, Boole, Bronfenbrenner, Calsamiglia, and others.
    - Alphabetical files, notes and printed material (Box 154)
      - Alphabetical, Cass-Faber (Box 154)
      - Chipman, 4 folders (Box 154)
      - Community indifference curves (Box 154)
      - Demsetz, monopolistic competition (Box 154)
      - Hurwicz, Design of mechanisms for resource allocation, Ely Lecture, 1974, 2 folders (Box 154)
    - Alphabetical Files (Box 155)
      - Faden-Kolm (alpha files) (Box 155)
        Papers and Hurwicz's notes on Fed. Reserve seminar, 1974; folders on Faden, Fan, Faulhaber, Feldman, Ferejohn, Foley, Frisch, Frobenius problem, Iwanek, Karlin, Katzner, Kolm, Jordan, and others.
      - Hurwicz/Reiter, proposal (1988), notes and research on Institutions, 11 folders (Box 155)
    - Alphabetical Files (Box 156)
      - Laffont-Peleg (Box 156)
        Folders with papers and notes on Laffont/Maskin, Lucas, Majumdar, Mas-Colell, Maschler, Marimon, Marshak, Nakamura, and others. There is one folder on non-linear pricing.
    - Alphabetical Files and Notes, Papers (Box 157)
      - Pazner-Reiersøl (Box 157)
        Folders with papers and notes on Postlewaite, Plott, and others. Includes a 1949 Cowles Commission paper on Identifiability of a linear relation between variables which are subject to error, by Olav Reiersøl.
      - Thomson, William, Kolm triangle, Walrasian allocations, and other topics, 2 folders (Box 157)
      - Econometric society, aide memoire (scope of society and bylaws, etc.), 1960s (Box 157)
      - Hurwicz, Evans, Optimality and informational efficiency - notes, proposal for Standford symposium on mathematical methods, 1959 (Box 157)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, Jordan, original notes and equations, 1978, 3 folders (Box 157)
      - Hurwicz, Optimality properties in a decentralized economy, undated paper, typewritten draft, clean copy (Box 157)
      - Announcement and prospectus of planned community in Colorado, 1911 (photocopy) (Box 157)
      - Handwritten notes: "Extension of Sol'ns... Arnold, maximal soluttions, with Richter over the phone," 1981 (Box 157)
      - Transparencies (Box 157)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 158)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, Optimization and Lagrange Multipliers paper, 1995 (Box 158)
      - Collaborations with and papers by Nishimura, Koopmans, Tesfation, Libecap (several folders) (Box 158)
      - Reiter collaboration on Decentralized Mechanisms (sent by Fran Walker, assistant), 2000s, 5 folders (Box 158)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 159)
      - Reiter (Box 159)
      - Mangasarian, 1969 (Box 159)
      - Samuelson article with Hurwicz notes, 1958 (Box 159)
      - Clippings, Economics Alerts, 1996 (Box 159)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, 1998, 14 folders (Box 159)
      - Pure exchange, 2 folders (Box 159)
    - Articles, drafts, and printed material (Box 160)
      - Various papers by Fururbotn (drafts), 1994; Etzioni; Wettstein, and others (Box 160)
      - Hurwicz reprint, What has happened to the theory of games, American Economic Review, 1953 (Box 160)
      - Economic planning and the knowledge problem: a comment, draft and galley proof for Cato Journal, 1984 (Box 160)
      - Draft and reprint, Outcome functions yielding Walrasian and Lindahl allocations at Nash Equilibrium points, 1976 (Box 160)
      - Reprint, Inventing new institutions (Box 160)
      - Collaboration with Jordan/Kannai, 1981 (Box 160)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, 1997-1998, 5 folders (Box 160)
      - Handout, Dimensional Requirements (Box 160)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material, 1990s-2000s (Box 161)
      - Collaboration with Saari and Reiter (Box 161)
      - Reverse engineering (Box 161)
      - Flagpoles (Box 161)
      - Papers by Weingast and Sheple, Greg Dow, and others (Box 161)
    - Drafts, notes, printed materials and teaching materials (Box 162)
      - Papers by Spence, Guesnerie, Baumol, Hart, Stokey, others, on optimality, oligopolies, markets (Box 162)
      - Graduate School Symposium, 1987, 2 folders (Box 162)
      - Collaboration with Reiter, 1990s (Box 162)
      - Comments by Hurwicz, and comments sent to Hurwicz and Mirowski by Arrow, on Hotelling and the neoclassical dream paper by Mirowski and Hands, 1990s (Box 162)
    - Clippings, drafts and printed material (Box 163)
      - Radner (Box 163)
      - Rosefielde, 2 folders (Box 163)
      - Saijo, 2 folders (Box 163)
      - Saari on chaos (Box 163)
      - Soviet Union, Russia and Eastern European reconstruction, clippings/articles, 3 folders (Box 163)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 164)
      - Alphabetical, Saarbrucken-Utility Theory (Box 164)
        Includes Schultz, T., Shapley and Shubik, Sorenson, Takayama, Tian (Lindahl Implementation); folder on game theory from RAND (1950, Von Neumann and Brown); and file on USSR.
      - Utility theory - 1938, 1948 papers by Samuelson and others (Box 164)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 165)
      - Alphabetical Files, Verblunsky-Yano (Box 165)
        Also includes files on Neil Wallace, Webb, Woodford, and Yannelis (3 folders).
      - Alphabetical Files, Galasi-Hartman (Box 165)
        Also includes files on Gillies, Daniel Graham (2 folders), Goursat (2 folders), Graves, Hancock, Harsanyi (1966).
    - Clippings and printed material (Box 166)
      - Alphabetical Files, Hartman-Humorous Science (Box 166)
        Includes files on Philip Hartman, Walter Heller, and Rhoda Howard on Canadian refugees, and poems by her on the holocaust.
      - Clippings on Poland, Soviet Union, refugees (including Soviet Jews), environment, tobacco industry, economics, and Hurwicz's activities at University, 9 folders (Box 166)
    - Clippings, notes and printed material (Box 167)
      - Clippings: archaeology; bonds; Hurwicz; political climate of Eastern Europe, United States and Russia; 1968 Democratic Convention (Hurwicz served as delegate); and weather forecasts (Box 167)
      - Hurwicz's papers, 1990s - offer to publish; letter from Duke on collections (Box 167)
      - Maskin and Sojøstrøm (1990s) (Box 167)
      - J.R. Commons, 1936 (Box 167)
      - Hurwicz - Coase invariance theorem, draft, 1997 (Box 167)
      - Battacharya and Majumdar paper (Box 167)
    - Correspondence, drafts, notes and printed material (Box 168)
      - Correspondence, including 2000 mailing about Holocaust reparations (Box 168)
      - Collaboration with Reiter (Box 168)
      - Offer curves, 2002 (Box 168)
      - Endowment game, 2000-2002 (Box 168)
      - Lindahl equilibria, 2002 (Box 168)
      - Various papers by Hurwicz, 1996-1999 (Box 168)
      - Hurwicz, Implementation with unknown endowments in a two-trader pure exchange economy (draft), 2002 (Box 168)
    - Correspondence, drafts, notes and printed material (Box 169)
      - Various papers and research notes, Hurwicz, 1996-1999, 5 folders (Box 169)
      - Collaboration with Marschak - correspondence and notes on Mechanism with finite message spaces, 1982, 2 folders (Box 169)
      - Sonnenschein (Box 169)
      - Cosgrove (Box 169)
      - Plott (Box 169)
      - Saari, NBER conference, 1976 (Box 169)
      - Reiter (Box 169)
      - Radner (Box 169)
    - Drafts, notes and printed material (Box 170)
      - Russian math - many photocopied articles (Box 170)
      - Hurwicz, paper on manipulative Nash equilibrium, paper on public goods, 1970s (Box 170)